<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="HallOfShameList">
		<item >Some 1 star market comments :)
		</item>
	    <item >Load of crap!	What a load of crap, drains battery, not charges battery. Avoid!!!
	    </item>
	    <item >Fail.	Read the Note: part at the bottom of the app description.
	    </item>
	    <item >Troll trap.....	What is this crap...lol....just cover your light sensor and it will jot work......don\'t believe everything you read or download...lmfao....just stupid
	    </item>
	    <item >HTC	This app is bs I have had it in the sun for an hour and its still at 84%
	    </item>
	    <item >Total waste of time.	This app is a joke. It\'s a basic light meter (think camera). This will only drain your battery as it runs.
		</item>
		<item >Crap	This entire app is a scam! If you read any good reviews they are completely fake and should not be considered. Please do not download
		</item>
		<item >Rubbish	Drained my battery quicker than it charged it
		</item>
		<item >Scam!	This app does not work, if you download it click the help button and read wat it says, it actually tells u it doesn\'t work!
		</item>
		<item >Read the full description. It is fake and meant to be fun to trick your friends. So you who say It\'s working must be smoking some real good stuff.lol
		</item>
		<item >Useless	Maker of this app is really idiot.... donot waste time to download this app....in " help "he tells how he is making fool of us... now we can make others too... nd he also say we should give it five star... coz we r idiots nd fool.... he he... actully mr maker ur really mentally retarded....
		</item>
		<item >Useless	It didnt charge my cell...insted made my battery low!!!! How lame
		</item>
		<item >Fooling	It a geek.....my battrry just drain..when this app is running..uninstalled..
		</item>
		<item >Lame	It says that the room is too dark and it needs to be in a very bright place to charge or no light.
		</item>
		<item >What a joke!	This app should be banned, it doesn\'t charge ur battery it drains it!if I could rate it no stars I would!
		</item>
		<item >DOESNT WORK...!!	WTF....!! Dnt dwnload it...!!
		</item>
		<item >Comment	Fake. It doesn\'t work
		</item>
		<item >go 2 hell ..	maker of this app is the idiot , in legal and lawful language he is minor and of unsound mind ! do not download , its all crap .. fk u Szlab .. go 2 hell 
		</item>
		<item >Read full description	Guy thinks he is cool by tricking people. I reported it and hope people will follow
		</item>
		<item >Its jst a picture I guess by the size...nt wrking....uninstalling....
		</item>
		<item >Wouldn\'t work	Not working on galaxy notes…
		</item>
		<item >Is this a gag app?	Does not charge my Samsung Galaxy S
		</item>
		<item >don\'t install	who ever made it is a idiot
		</item>
		<item >Worthless prank	Don\'t even try. Drains your battery!!!
		</item>
		<item >Absolutely pointless. DOES NOT CHARGE YA PHONE. The creater of this app needs to get a life.
		</item>
		<item >crap	Not even worth single star.. it jus vibrates n displays as charging wen kept under light.. Never does as it says.
		</item>
		<item >Not working.. AT ALL	This is just fake shit!! I\'d rather bring the developers\' faces down in the dirty canals
		</item>
		<item >Drain	Drain battery life. Do not work for Samsung galaxy s 2.
		</item>
		<item >FAKE	Are you really going to belive this? Anw it drained my battery rather than charging it
		</item>
		<item >Dosent work on galaxy s2	Good idea but dose not charge galaxy s2. Only drains battery. I had it sitting it the sun for about 20 min and lost half my battery life. I wonder if its just my phone. It seems there\'s a lot of ppl that say it works.
		</item>
		<item >Worst app ever seen	F##king idiotic app..the developer is begging to gv him nice rating in the help menu....fully waste of time...crappy app
		</item>
		<item >Crappy ... Such apps should be banned
		</item>
		<item >WTF	Instead of charging this app consumes energy, do not down load
		</item>
		<item >SAMSUNG GALAXY SII	This crap app doesnt work on my phone, it drains the battery dramatically instead if charging it!
		</item>
		<item >Please read more on the android market :)
		</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>