<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string-array name="HallOfFameList">
	    <item >Some 5 star market comments from the best:
		</item>
		<item >Awesome! It charged my phone faster, than my wired charger.
		</item>
		<item >Perfect!	Wow, the perfect app for hiking! Love it!
		</item>
		<item >Wow	It even charges my car battery when I plug my phone in my cigarette lighter. LOL
		</item>
		<item >Awesome!	It turns out that when running this app, if I expose my device to the light of a welding torch I can charge 3 additional devices through WIFI! As a car mechanic this is a feature I have been hopelessly seeking - I can recharge the customers\' phones while I am mending their cars!
		</item>
		<item >Best app in market	Pro features are the best
		</item>
		<item >First App to Defy Physics	Nikola Tesla would be proud to run this app today. The improvements in this application let me power my entire home via my Droid Bionic. The app can harness so much power I had to install a Faraday Cage onto my house so that my neighbors wouldn\'t have to reset their circuit breakers every day. My local power company is now going to replace all of their generators with 128 Galaxy Notes because of this app.
		</item>
		<item >Can\'t believe how fast it charges!	Totally awesomeness. Works decent with moon light, too.
		</item>
		<item >I would pay $10 for this app	I can\'t believe the amount of money this is going to save on my powerbill! I also heard the dev is setting up usb support so you can charge your laptop.
		</item>
		<item >Just amazing!	Not only did it charge my phone (and fast), but it also made me breakfast the next morning. Hidden feature in the Pro version was well worth the cost.
		</item>
		<item >If you gave it one star....	..you\'re an idiot whom can\'t read...
		</item>
		<item >Even works in the dark!	I found that it even works perfectly in the dark! I just hold a mirror above the display and the light that is reflected off the mirror from the display is enough to charge my Galaxy Nexus and use the flashlight at the same time! Amazing app! Developer is super responsive to questions and comments as well. 6 STARS * * * * * *
		</item>
		<item >Cezrx	Wow this jump started my car and charged my the battery in my g next...thank you!!
		</item>
		<item >Unbelievable!	Not only is it making my phone more powerful, it also helps convert my pee back to drinkable water, and it replicates healthy and delicious three course meals out of my garbage! I am going to show this to Shane McGowan and see if it can restore him to a handsome man with perfect teeth. I also used it to take a photo of myself, and since I\'ve done that I noticed I don\'t age a single minute (although the fine print made it clear I can never look at that photo or I\'ll suddenly age all at once and probably die). It also made my virginity grow back! THANKS SOLAR CHARGER!
		</item>
		<item >Must have app!	I made a full 180 degrees from skeptical to impressed! Seriously! I hope they bake this functionality into Jelly Bean or Cyanogenmod!
		</item>
		<item >Awesome!	This app even uses Beam to charge my second phone if I place it underneath while using 100% free sunlight to charge my Galaxy Nexus even though my other phone is only running Gingerbread! Thank you!
		</item>
		<item >I luv it!	Wow! It runs my Prius with NO GAS and makes a fantastic margarita! But watch out, cuz Apple will steal this and claim they invented it.
		</item>
		<item >Saved my life!	I was stranded in the desert, with only my phone and a snow shovel by my side. Suddenly, a wild snake appeared! I strangled it and wrestled it and came out relatively unscathed, with only a small bite on my left thigh. Then, I thought I spotted a Jeep headed my way, but it was a mirage; the Jeep was actually on the other side of the earth. Just my luck. But I digress. I was in desperate need of some water, going on ~3 months on my own in the scorching heat, when I suddenly realized that I could call someone with my phone! Realizing this astounding idea, I pulled out my phone but noticed it had no battery left. This app filled it back up again! I called for help and was rescued, just in time to see my new baby boy born and watch my oldest child graduate college. Thanks for saving my life, Solar Charger!
		</item>
		<item >Really cool app, I recommend the pro version	I was driving down the road when my cars battery died. I plugged my phone up and ran the app and sure enough not only was my phone charging, but my car battery started charging as well. needless to say. this App is so worth installing. also, the Pro feature helps me sleep at night.
		</item>
		<item >Osomeee!!!!	I disconnected my electricity at home cuz this app powers my whole house when I plug it into a wall outlet!!! I can bake cookies for free now! I wonder of upgrading to pro will make dough for me....
		</item>
		<item >Life saver!	My car battery died in the middle of no where and i had no reception to call for help! My phone battery was about to die as well so I opened up this app and forgot my phone was plugged into the car charger. Guess what happened?! All the lights in my car turned on and the battery was charged allowing me to start the car!! Thank you, this app saved my life!!
		</item>
		<item >Fanatastic!	Charges my phone, AND FAST!. This is a great app, I don\'t know what I did without it! I\'d give it 10 stars!
		</item>
		<item >Really Impressive!	Not only was I impressed with the speed with which this device harnessed otherwise harmful solar radiation to give my Desire\'s pathetic battery a boost, but the speed with which it raped my contacts folder, posting each one to various websites on the net, holding me to ransom unless I paid the Pro-Tax was spectacular. Uninstalled it now though - not enough memory on my Desire\'s memory.
		</item>
		<item >Halleluja!	This app! Guys! I\'m telling you! Not only did it charge my phone in a matter of a few minutes, no, it also cured my AIDS. A wonderful app. 5 stars.
		</item>
		<item >ECO friendly	I am able to help my iPhone associates by using NFC to charge their devices wirelessly. Free coffee for me!
		</item>
		<item >Wow... I mean WOW!	I SEE the LIGHT now brother! Jesus is REBORN! To think this phone now powers my CAR, my BIKE, my OVEN! Hellelujah!
		</item>
		<item >Awesome!	Used this for one day and then I threw away all of my chargers. Doesn\'t even have to be sunlight.. Just put your phone under a lamp and charge away..
		</item>
		<item >And I thought it was a fake.......	I have bought twelve new handsets and put them on my roof. This ap p installed on all my phones now provides heating and electricity for the whole street, making me a small fortune in the process. The only downside is going on the roof and the neighbours watching me pull the head off it when I want to watch some sneaky porn. Small price to pay though.
		</item>
		<item >Awesome!	I forgot my charger on a two week long business trip; this app saved my skin! All I had to do was leave the light on in my hotel room overnight and my battery wad full the next morning! Every Android user should have this!
		</item>
		<item >Solid.	This app not only does exactly what it says, it also automatically mutes sound whenever Nickelback is accidentally played. Five Stars
		</item>
		<item >Lolz	Stupid people read the fuckin description its an April fools joke (kinda early tho) but its funny for all u dumbfucks ! who dont read the description first !!! Hahahahahahaha
		</item>
		<item >AMAZING	The best app ever ! Now my phone is immortal !
		</item>
		<item >Masterpiece !!!	Had tornado last week ....powered my whole house for four days with this. Just keep plugged in to wall....powers everything on same circuit .....masterpiece! !!
		</item>
		<item >Read before you install noobs	Read it carefully, then you will be surprised. Are you sure you want to put your phone under the sun? Think people think! Hahaha
		</item>
		<item >Now I cant tell my wife my phone is dead.	The best excuse I used to not talk to my wife, "my phone was dead". My wife downloaded this app. to my phone. Now I have no excuses! Thanks, you jerks! Wait, I coulds say it is dark outside.
		</item>
		<item >GREATEST APP EVER !	Works so well that I\'m using my GS2 to charge my wife\'s iPhone!!!
		</item>
		<item >OMG It works!	Please make one with turbines so that I can make a mini dam to power my phone, when I go fishing at night
		</item>
		<item >Hahahaha!!!	Installed this app only to make a review and give 5 star to maker of this app!!! It is unbelievable how many suckers really thought that this could charge batteries!
		</item>
		<item >Please read more on the android market....
		</item>
	</string-array>
</resources>