<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="hello">charging...</string>
	<string name="app_name">Solar Charger</string>
	<string name="settings">Settings</string>
	<string name="help">Help!</string>
	<string name="exit">Exit</string>
	<string name="helpLong">
	<![CDATA[
	<font color=\'white\'>

<h2>Help</h2>

<p>Wow! you pressed the help menu!</p>
<p>You are one of those rare users brave enough to read up on something they are using!
Maximum respect!<p>

<p>A small hint about this app:</p>
<ul>
<li>This is not charging your battery! Of course not! It\'s not rocket science to figure out that would never work. It is impossible to solar charge you phone through its display, without a physical solar panel. </li>
<li>This application is probably draining your battery :)</li>
</ul>

<p>Does anything work then?</p>
<ul>
<li>The light VU meter detects the amount of light what the light sensor receives</li>
<li>You can open/close the VU meter by pressing it</li>
<li>Your battery level -displayed on the top- shows correct percentage</li>
<li>If the external light is above a certain level it plays a nice animation for charging</li>
<li>You can change the solar panel background</li>
<li>You can prevent the device from going to sleep</li>
</ul>

<p>What good is this app then?</p>
<ul>
<li>After a couple of drinks it is fun to show your friends what a brilliant app you have.</li>
<li>It was a good study for this small project to see the Android workflow from sdk install to actual release.</li>
<li>Each time I browse the Android market I find idiots giving one star to an application because of their own lame stupidness.
I wanted to collect some of those people and their comments. So I had to create something obviously not working :)
To confuse those llamas feel free to give 5 star rating with comments like \'wow it works\' or \'it saved my life\'... Be creative ;)</li>
</ul>

<p>Update 1.1</p>
<ul>
<li>Fixed an initial VU meter animation issue</li>
<li>Now the app fakes light sensor values if the device not supports light sensor.</li>
</ul>

<p>Thank you:</p>
I would like to say thank you for PoGergo for the app review. 
And I also thanks for the support of all my friends and collagues who supported the app with nice comments, and promoting the app. <br/>
<ul>
<li>So far it seems that there are more than 1000 user out there with a sense of humour.</li>
<li>Unfortunately there are more than 500 retards...</li>
</ul>
<p>But heads up! We are still winning :)</p>
<br/>
<br/>
</font>
		]]>
	</string>
	<string name="set_preferences">Preferences</string>
	<string name="setings_category_first">Main</string>
	<string name="setings_bg_list">Solar Panel Type</string>
	<string name="setings_bg_list_sum">You can choose the solar panel type here.</string>
	<string name="setings_keep_awake">Keep Device Awake</string>
	<string name="setings_keep_awake_sum">Checking this prevents the device to switch off while sleeping.</string>
	
	<string name="str_FeedbackTextDark">Too dark here.\nPut the device into direct light!</string>
	<string name="str_FeedbackTextCharging">Charging...</string>
	
	<string name="hint_tap_vu_hide">Tap the VUMeter to hide it.</string>
</resources>
